theorchidboutique.com 2008-08-28

# The Orchid Boutique

|  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|   
---  
  
| **Privacy**  
---  
| **•** | 

Our primary goal is to provide you with an exciting and fulfilling shopping experience. To that end, we collect and assimilate non-personal information from you and others to determine the products and services most preferred. Additionally, we use this information to better understand your experience on our web site; such as areas most visited, or how the site is being navigated. The ongoing development of non-personal information will be used to continually improve your experience at The Orchid Boutique.  
  
---|---  
**•** | 

Your privacy is of utmost concern to us. We have in place policies and procedures that protect your personal information. Any use of this information will be handled in a responsible manner.  

**Use of Cookies**  
| **•** | 

Our site is designed to provide fast and efficient, yet extremely personalized service to all of our customers. We have in use on our site a browser feature known as cookies. Cookies are small text files that allow us to uniquely identify each person that visits our site. These cookies are stored on your computer and are only accessible to us.  
  
---|---  
**•** | 

We do not store any personal information such as your name, phone number or credit card information in these cookies. They are used to help us understand how you navigate our site and to improve your shopping experience. Any information that is obtained from these cookies is strictly non-personal and used for technical purposes only.  

**Collection of Personal Information**  
  
For an online purchase by credit card, you will be asked to provide your name, billing and shipping address, phone number, e-mail address and credit card information.  
  
**We collect the above information to:**  
| **•** | 

Complete your transaction.  
  
---|---  
**•** | 

Keep you informed regarding the status of your order.  
  
**•** | 

Additionally, we would use the information to respond to any inquiries you may have, or to include you on our mailing list. If you would like your personal information removed from this list, please send an email to [customerservice@theorchidboutique.com.](mailto:customerservice@theorchidboutique.com)  

**Security**  
| **•** | 

The Orchid Boutique is committed to providing you with a safe and secure shopping experience. Your online credit card transactions are protected by Verisign (SSL), the encryption technology that ensures safe Internet transmission of your personal information.  
  
---|---  
**•** | 

To obtain these certificates, The Orchid Boutique had to go undergo investigation and meet various security guidelines. For this reason we can ascertain that a credit card purchase on The Orchid Boutique is very safe.
